zs.com 2019-07-20

# Privacy Policy Highlights | ZS

## ZS Associates  
Online Privacy Policy  
Last Updated: April 12, 2019

## Privacy Policy Highlights

ZS is committed to protecting the privacy of our clients and anyone we engage with on their behalf, as well as any visitors to our Web site. The following are highlights from our Privacy Policy: 

**Data Collection**

  * We collect both personal data that you provide to us and personal data that is automatically collected via our Web site.
  * Your data will be stored in our systems and may be supplemented by public information about you available from third parties.
  * Data we collect is kept only so long as is necessary for the purpose for which it was collected.

**Cookies**

  * We use cookies on our Web site to facilitate and enhance user experience. You may use your device’s or browser’s options to disable cookies, but that may affect the functionality of the Web site. You can read our Cookie Policy here.

**How Your Data is Used**

  * Your data is used to provide you with information or materials you request.
  * We may use data you provide to us to send you information about our products or services that you may be interested in, where permissible or if you have opted in to receiving such information.
  * We may use your data for market research.
  * We may use your data to personalize and enhance your experience on our Web site.
  * We process data from our clients subject to our clients’ discretion and control.

**Your Choices**

  * You may disable cookies on your device or browser.
  * You may unsubscribe from any e-mail programs you opt into.
  * You may contact us at [dataprivacy@zs.com](mailto:dataprivacy@zs.com) for information on opting out or to access or update the data we have about you.

Read our full Privacy Policy.

If you are a current, former, or prospective ZSer, you may also click here.

For India-specific information, click here.
